{
  "questions": [
    {
      "questiontext": "What OSI layer is FTP",
      "answerchoice1": "Session",
      "answerchoice2": "Application",
      "answerchoice3": "Data Link",
      "answerchoice4": "Network",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "What OSI layer is RADIUS, TACACS+",
      "answerchoice1": "Session",
      "answerchoice2": "Application",
      "answerchoice3": "Data Link",
      "answerchoice4": "Network",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "What OSI layer is SONET, ATM, DSL",
      "answerchoice1": "Session",
      "answerchoice2": "Physical",
      "answerchoice3": "Data Link",
      "answerchoice4": "Network",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "What OSI layer is end-to-end reliability",
      "answerchoice1": "Session",
      "answerchoice2": "Transport",
      "answerchoice3": "Data Link",
      "answerchoice4": "Network",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "What OSI layer is convert data",
      "answerchoice1": "Session",
      "answerchoice2": "Application",
      "answerchoice3": "Presentation",
      "answerchoice4": "Network",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "What OSI layer is ARP, PPP, SLIP?",
      "answerchoice1": "Session",
      "answerchoice2": "Application",
      "answerchoice3": "Data Link",
      "answerchoice4": "Network",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "S/MIME integrity?",
      "answerchoice1": "DSA, 3DES, RSA",
      "answerchoice2": "MD5, DSA, SHA-1, X.509",
      "answerchoice3": "DSA, RSA, X.509",
      "answerchoice4": "DSA, RSA",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "S/MIME authentication?",
      "answerchoice1": "DSA, 3DES, RSA",
      "answerchoice2": "MD5, DSA, SHA-1, X.509",
      "answerchoice3": "DSA, RSA, X.509",
      "answerchoice4": "DSA, RSA",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "S/MIME confidentiality?",
      "answerchoice1": "DSA, 3DES, RSA",
      "answerchoice2": "MD5, DSA, SHA-1, X.509",
      "answerchoice3": "DSA, RSA, X.509",
      "answerchoice4": "DES, RSA, RC4, D-H",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "S/MIME non-repudiation?",
      "answerchoice1": "DSA, 3DES, RSA",
      "answerchoice2": "MD5, DSA, SHA-1, X.509",
      "answerchoice3": "DSA, RSA, X.509",
      "answerchoice4": "DSA, RSA",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "Credit card details?",
      "answerchoice1": "DSA, 3DES, RSA",
      "answerchoice2": "MD5, DSA, SHA-1, X.509",
      "answerchoice3": "DSA, RSA, X.509",
      "answerchoice4": "SET",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "PAP?",
      "answerchoice1": "Authentication",
      "answerchoice2": "Identifcation",
      "answerchoice3": "Confidentiality",
      "answerchoice4": "Non-repudiation",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "3-way handshake repeated during session?",
      "answerchoice1": "PAP",
      "answerchoice2": "CHAP",
      "answerchoice3": "EAP",
      "answerchoice4": "TACACS+",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "Framework?",
      "answerchoice1": "PAP",
      "answerchoice2": "CHAP",
      "answerchoice3": "EAP",
      "answerchoice4": "TACACS+",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "54Mbps, OFDM, 5GHz?",
      "answerchoice1": "802.11a",
      "answerchoice2": "802.11b",
      "answerchoice3": "802.11g",
      "answerchoice4": "802.11i",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "11Mbps, DSSS, 2.4GHz?",
      "answerchoice1": "802.11a",
      "answerchoice2": "802.11b",
      "answerchoice3": "802.11g",
      "answerchoice4": "802.11i",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "54Mbps, OFDM, 2.4GHzM?",
      "answerchoice1": "802.11a",
      "answerchoice2": "802.11b",
      "answerchoice3": "802.11g",
      "answerchoice4": "802.11i",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "amendment, interference, Euro?",
      "answerchoice1": "802.11h",
      "answerchoice2": "802.11b",
      "answerchoice3": "802.11g",
      "answerchoice4": "802.11i",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "Encryption?",
      "answerchoice1": "802.11a",
      "answerchoice2": "802.11b",
      "answerchoice3": "802.11g",
      "answerchoice4": "802.11i",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "600Mbps, MIMO, dynamic freq?",
      "answerchoice1": "802.11a",
      "answerchoice2": "802.11n",
      "answerchoice3": "802.11g",
      "answerchoice4": "802.11i",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "copying data?",
      "answerchoice1": "Bluejacking",
      "answerchoice2": "Bluesnarfing",
      "answerchoice3": "Bluebugging",
      "answerchoice4": " ",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "issue AT commands?",
      "answerchoice1": "Bluejacking",
      "answerchoice2": "Bluesnarfing",
      "answerchoice3": "Bluebugging",
      "answerchoice4": " ",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "questiontext": "sending unwanted messages?",
      "answerchoice1": "Bluejacking",
      "answerchoice2": "Bluesnarfing",
      "answerchoice3": "Bluebugging",
      "answerchoice4": " ",
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}